Inside Albany Records
Inside Albany Records
- Videorecordings
  - Videorecordings, 1991
    - No. 1740, 1991-03-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0672 (Box 70)
    - No. 1741, 1991-03-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0672 (Box 70)
    - No. 1742, 1991-03-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0673 (Box 70)
    - No. 1743, 1991-04-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0673 (Box 70)
    - No. 1744, 1991-04-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0673 (Box 70)
    - No. 1745, 1991-04-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0674 (Box 70)
    - No. 1746, 1991-04-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0674 (Box 70)
    - No. 1747, 1991-05-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0674 (Box 70)
    - No. 1748, 1991-05-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0675 (Box 70)
    - No. 1749, 1991-05-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0675 (Box 70)
    - No. 1750, 1991-05-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0675 (Box 70)
    - No. 1751, 1991-05-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0676 (Box 70)
    - No. 1752, 1991-06-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0676 (Box 70)
    - No. 1801, 1991-06-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0676 (Box 70)
    - No. 1802, 1991-06-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0677 (Box 71)
    - No. 1803, 1991-06-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0677 (Box 71)
    - No. 1804, 1991-07-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0677 (Box 71)
    - No. 1805, 1991-07-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0678 (Box 71)
    - No. 1806, 1991-07-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0678 (Box 71)
    - No. 1807, 1991-07-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0678 (Box 71)
    - No. 1808, 1991-08-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0679 (Box 71)
    - No. 1809, 1991-08-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0679 (Box 71)
    - No. 1810, 1991-08-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0679 (Box 71)
    - No. 1811, 1991-08-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0680 (Box 71)
    - No. 1812, 1991-08-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0680 (Box 71)
    - No. 1813, 1991-09-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0680 (Box 71)
    - No. 1814, 1991-09-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0681 (Box 71)
    - No. 1815, 1991-09-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0681 (Box 71)
    - No. 1816, 1991-09-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0681 (Box 71)
    - No. 1817, 1991-10-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0682 (Box 71)
    - No. 1818, 1991-10-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0682 (Box 71)
    - No. 1819, 1991-10-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0682 (Box 71)
    - No. 1820, 1991-10-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0683 (Box 71)
    - No. 1821, 1991-11-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0683 (Box 71)
    - No. 1822, 1991-11-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0683 (Box 71)
    - No. 1823, 1991-11-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0684 (Box 71)
    - No. 1824, 1991-11-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0684 (Box 71)
    - No. 1825, 1991-11-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0684 (Box 71)
    - No. 1826, 1991-12-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0685 (Box 71)
    - No. 1827, 1991-12-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0685 (Box 71)
    - No. 1828, 1991-12-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0685 (Box 71)
    - No. 1829, 1991-12-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0686 (Box 72)
  - Videorecordings, 1992
    - No. 1830, 1992-01-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0686 (Box 72)
    - No. 1831, 1992-01-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0686 (Box 72)
    - No. 1832, 1992-01-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0687 (Box 72)
    - No. 1833, 1992-01-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0687 (Box 72)
    - No. 1834, 1992-01-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0687 (Box 72)
    - No. 1835, 1992-02-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0688 (Box 72)
    - No. 1836, 1992-02-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0688 (Box 72)
    - No. 1837, 1992-02-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0688 (Box 72)
    - No. 1838, 1992-02-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0689 (Box 72)
    - No. 1839, 1992-03-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0689 (Box 72)
    - No. 1840, 1992-03-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0689 (Box 72)
    - No. 1841, 1992-03-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0690 (Box 72)
    - No. 1842, 1992-03-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0690 (Box 72)
    - No. 1843, 1992-04-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0690 (Box 72)
    - No. 1844, 1992-04-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0691 (Box 72)
    - No. 1845, 1992-04-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0691 (Box 72)
    - No. 1846, 1992-04-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0691 (Box 72)
    - No. 1847, 1992-05-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0692 (Box 72)
    - No. 1848, 1992-05-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0692 (Box 72)
    - No. 1849, 1992-05-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0692 (Box 72)
    - No. 1850, 1992-05-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0693 (Box 72)
    - No. 1851, 1992-05-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0693 (Box 72)
    - No. 1852, 1992-06-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0693 (Box 72)
    - No. 1901, 1992-06-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0694 (Box 72)
    - No. 1902, 1992-06-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0694 (Box 72)
    - No. 1903, 1992-06-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0694 (Box 72)
    - No. 1904, 1992-07-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0695 (Box 73)
    - No. 1905, 1992-07-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0695 (Box 73)
    - No. 1906, 1992-07-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0695 (Box 73)
    - No. 1907, 1992-07-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0696 (Box 73)
    - No. 1908, 1992-07-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0696 (Box 73)
    - No. 1909, 1992-08-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0696 (Box 73)
    - No. 1910, 1992-08-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0697 (Box 73)
    - No. 1911, 1992-08-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0697 (Box 73)
    - No. 1912, 1992-08-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0697 (Box 73)
    - No. 1913, 1992-09-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0698 (Box 73)
    - No. 1914, 1992-09-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0698 (Box 73)
    - No. 1915, 1992-09-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0698 (Box 73)
    - No. 1916, 1992-09-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0699 (Box 73)
    - No. 1917, 1992-10-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0699 (Box 73)
    - No. 1918, 1992-10-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0699 (Box 73)
    - No. 1919, 1992-10-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0700 (Box 73)
    - No. 1920, 1992-10-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0700 (Box 73)
    - No. 1921, 1992-10-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0700 (Box 73)
    - No. 1922, 1992-11-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0701 (Box 73)
    - No. 1923, 1992-11-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0701 (Box 73)
    - No. 1924, 1992-11-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0701 (Box 73)
    - No. 1925, 1992-11-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0702 (Box 73)
    - No. 1926, 1992-12-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0702 (Box 73)
    - No. 1927, 1992-12-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0702 (Box 73)
    - No. 1928, 1992-12-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0703 (Box 73)
    - No. 1929, 1992-12-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0703 (Box 73)
  - Videorecordings, 1993
    - No. 1930, 1993-01-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0703 (Box 73)
    - No. 1931, 1993-01-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0704 (Box 74)
    - No. 1932, 1993-01-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0704 (Box 74)
    - No. 1933, 1993-01-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0704 (Box 74)
    - No. 1934, 1993-01-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0705 (Box 74)
    - No. 1935, 1993-02-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0705 (Box 74)
    - No. 1936, 1993-02-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0705 (Box 74)
    - No. 1937, 1993-02-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0706 (Box 74)
    - No. 1938, 1993-02-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0706 (Box 74)
    - No. 1939, 1993-03-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0706 (Box 74)
    - No. 1940, 1993-03-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0707 (Box 74)
    - No. 1941, 1993-03-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0707 (Box 74)
    - No. 1942, 1993-03-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0707 (Box 74)
    - No. 1943, 1993-04-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0708 (Box 74)
    - No. 1944, 1993-04-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0708 (Box 74)
    - No. 1945, 1993-04-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0708 (Box 74)
    - No. 1946, 1993-04-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0709 (Box 74)
    - No. 1947, 1993-04-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0709 (Box 74)
    - No. 1948, 1993-05-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0709 (Box 74)
    - No. 1949, 1993-05-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0710 (Box 74)
    - No. 1950, 1993-05-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0710 (Box 74)
    - No. 1951, 1993-05-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0710 (Box 74)
    - No. 1952, 1993-06-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0711 (Box 74)
    - No. 2001, 1993-06-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0711 (Box 74)
    - No. 2002, 1993-06-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0711 (Box 74)
    - No. 2003, 1993-06-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0712 (Box 74)
    - No. 2004, 1993-07-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0712 (Box 74)
    - No. 2005, 1993-07-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0712 (Box 74)
    - No. 2006, 1993-07-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0713 (Box 75)
    - No. 2007, 1993-07-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0713 (Box 75)
    - No. 2008, 1993-07-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0713 (Box 75)
    - No. 2009, 1993-08-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0714 (Box 75)
    - No. 2010, 1993-08-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0714 (Box 75)
    - No. 2011, 1993-08-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0714 (Box 75)
    - No. 2012, 1993-08-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0715 (Box 75)
    - No. 2013, 1993-09-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0715 (Box 75)
    - No. 2014, 1993-09-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0715 (Box 75)
    - No. 2015, 1993-09-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0716 (Box 75)
    - No. 2016, 1993-09-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0716 (Box 75)
    - No. 2017, 1993-09-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0716 (Box 75)
    - No. 2018, 1993-10-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0717 (Box 75)
    - No. 2019, 1993-10-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0717 (Box 75)
    - No. 2020, 1993-10-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0717 (Box 75)
    - No. 2021, 1993-10-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0718 (Box 75)
    - No. 2022, 1993-11-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0718 (Box 75)
    - No. 2023, 1993-11-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0718 (Box 75)
    - No. 2024, 1993-11-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0719 (Box 75)
    - No. 2025, 1993-11-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0719 (Box 75)
    - No. 2026, 1993-12-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0719 (Box 75)
    - No. 2027, 1993-12-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0720 (Box 75)
    - No. 2028, 1993-12-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0720 (Box 75)
    - No. 2029, 1993-12-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0720 (Box 75)
    - No. 2030, 1993-12-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0721 (Box 75)
  - Videorecordings, 1994
    - No. 2031, 1994-01-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0721 (Box 75)
    - No. 2032, 1994-01-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0721 (Box 75)
    - No. 2033, 1994-01-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0722 (Box 76)
    - No. 2034, 1994-01-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0722 (Box 76)
    - No. 2035, 1994-02-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0722 (Box 76)
    - No. 2036, 1994-02-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0723 (Box 76)
    - No. 2037, 1994-02-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0723 (Box 76)
    - No. 2038, 1994-02-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0723 (Box 76)
    - No. 2039, 1994-03-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0724 (Box 76)
    - No. 2040, 1994-03-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0724 (Box 76)
    - No. 2041, 1994-03-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0724 (Box 76)
    - No. 2042, 1994-03-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0725 (Box 76)
    - No. 2043, 1994-03-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0725 (Box 76)
    - No. 2044, 1994-04-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0725 (Box 76)
    - No. 2045, 1994-04-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0726 (Box 76)
    - No. 2046, 1994-04-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0726 (Box 76)
    - No. 2047, 1994-04-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0726 (Box 76)
    - No. 2048, 1994-05-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0729 (Box 76)
    - Inside Albany Special: Constitutional Convention, 1994-05-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0727 (Box 76)
    - Inside Albany Special: Constitutional Convention, 1994-05-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; dub; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0728; duplicate (Box 76)
    - No. 2049, 1994-05-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0729 (Box 76)
    - No. 2050, 1994-05-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0729 (Box 76)
    - No. 2051, 1994-05-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0730 (Box 76)
    - No. 2052, 1994-06-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0730 (Box 76)
    - Inside Albany: LCA Show, 1994-06-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0730; Legislative Correspondents Association Show (musical comedy revue) (Box 76)
    - No. 2101, 1994-06-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0731 (Box 77)
    - No. 2102, 1994-06-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0731 (Box 77)
    - No. 2103, 1994-06-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0731 (Box 77)
    - No. 2104, 1994-06-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0732 (Box 77)
    - No. 2105, 1994-07-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0732 (Box 77)
    - No. 2106, 1994-07-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0732 (Box 77)
    - No. 2107, 1994-07-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0733 (Box 77)
    - No. 2108, 1994-07-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0733 (Box 77)
    - No. 2109 through 2112, 8/4/94-8/25/94; Not present in the collection.
    - No. 2113, 1994-09-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0733 (Box 77)
    - No. 2114, 9/8/94; Not present in the collection.
    - No. 2115, 1994-09-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0734 (Box 77)
    - No. 2116, 1994-09-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0734 (Box 77)
    - Inside Albany Special: Governor's Race, 1994-09-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0735 (Box 77)
    - No. 2117, 1994-09-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0734 (Box 77)
    - No. 2118, 1994-10-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0736 (Box 77)
    - No. 2119, 1994-10-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0736 (Box 77)
    - No. 2120, 1994-10-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0736 (Box 77)
    - No. 2121, 1994-11-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0737 (Box 77)
    - No. 2122, 1994-11-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0737 (Box 77)
    - No. 2123, 1994-11-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0737 (Box 77)
    - No. 2124, 1994-11-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0738 (Box 77)
    - No. 2125, 1994-12-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0738 (Box 77)
    - No. 2126, 1994-12-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0738 (Box 77)
    - No. 2127, 1994-12-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0739 (Box 77)
    - No. 2128, 1994-12-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0739 (Box 77)
    - No. 2129, 1994-12-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0739 (Box 77)
  - Videorecordings, 1995
    - No. 2130, 1995-01-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0740 (Box 78)
    - No. 2131, 1995-01-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0740 (Box 78)
    - No. 2132, 1995-01-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0740 (Box 78)
    - No. 2133, 1995-01-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0741 (Box 78)
    - No. 2134, 1995-02-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0741 (Box 78)
    - No. 2135, 1995-02-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0741 (Box 78)
    - No. 2136, 1995-02-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0742 (Box 78)
    - No. 2137, 1995-02-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0742 (Box 78)
    - No. 2138, 1995-03-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0742 (Box 78)
    - No. 2139, 1995-03-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0743 (Box 78)
    - No. 2140, 1995-03-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0743 (Box 78)
    - No. 2141, 1995-03-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0743 (Box 78)
    - No. 2142, 1995-03-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0744 (Box 78)
    - No. 2143, 1995-04-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0744 (Box 78)
    - No. 2144, 1995-04-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0744 (Box 78)
    - No. 2145, 1995-04-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0745 (Box 78)
    - No. 2146, 1995-04-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0745 (Box 78)
    - No. 2147, 1995-05-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0745 (Box 78)
    - No. 2148, 1995-05-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0746 (Box 78)
    - No. 2149, 1995-05-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0746 (Box 78)
    - No. 2150, 1995-05-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0746 (Box 78)
    - No. 2151, 1995-06-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0747 (Box 78)
    - No. 2152, 1995-06-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0747 (Box 78)
    - No. 2201, 1995-06-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0747 (Box 78)